(Penny:)Okay. Yeah, well, I'm just gonna go eat
my dinner elsewhere.
(Penny:)Maybe an airplane headed
for a mountainside.
Penny, wait. Aah.
(Leonard:)What is wrong with you?
[DOOR SLAMS]
(Sheldon:)I sense I may have crossed
some sort of line.
(Raj:)-Yeah, you--
-Don't tell him.
(Howard:)Let's see if he can figure it out.
(Penny:)-Ugh. I am so embarrassed.
-Please don't be mad.
(Penny:)-What did you tell them?
-Nothing bad.
(Leonard:)Just that last night was fine.
(Penny:)Fine? You said it was fine?
(Leonard:)Yeah. It's a perfectly good word.
You put it in front of "wine" or "dining"
and you've really got something.
(Leonard:)Okay, well, let me ask you this,
how was last night for you?
(Leonard:)It was...
(Howard:)...okay.
(Leonard:)Okay?